const englishWritingQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the first step in the writing process?",
    options: ["Editing", "Proofreading", "Revising", "Planning"],
    correct_option: "Planning",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of an introduction in an essay or report?",
    options: [
      "To summarize the main points",
      "To present the conclusion",
      "To engage the reader and introduce the topic",
      "To list references",
    ],
    correct_option: "To engage the reader and introduce the topic",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In a persuasive essay, what is the purpose of the body paragraphs?",
    options: [
      "To restate the thesis",
      "To provide background information",
      "To present the main arguments and evidence",
      "To conclude the essay",
    ],
    correct_option: "To present the main arguments and evidence",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of reviewing and improving the clarity and coherence of a written work?",
    options: ["Editing", "Proofreading", "Drafting", "Revising"],
    correct_option: "Revising",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a common style guide used for academic and professional writing?",
    options: [
      "APA",
      "Text message language",
      "Internet slang",
      "Casual writing",
    ],
    correct_option: "APA",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for unintentional copying of someone else's work without proper attribution?",
    options: ["Paraphrasing", "Plagiarism", "Quoting", "Citation"],
    correct_option: "Plagiarism",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is an important aspect of effective writing?",
    options: [
      "Using complex words to impress the reader",
      "Using proper grammar and punctuation",
      "Avoiding varied sentence structures",
      "Repeating the same idea in every paragraph",
    ],
    correct_option: "Using proper grammar and punctuation",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a conclusion in a research paper?",
    options: [
      "To introduce the topic",
      "To present new ideas",
      "To restate the main points and provide closure",
      "To criticize the research methods",
    ],
    correct_option: "To restate the main points and provide closure",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is a common type of writing used in business communication for conveying information and requests?",
    options: ["Memo", "Novel", "Poem", "Fairy tale"],
    correct_option: "Memo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of checking a written work for spelling and grammatical errors?",
    options: ["Revising", "Proofreading", "Brainstorming", "Editing"],
    correct_option: "Proofreading",
  },
];
export default englishWritingQuestions;
